{
    "subject": "resource/Youth's_Endearing_Charm",
    "predicate": "ontology/distributor",
    "object": "resource/Mutual_Film",
    "human_readable": "The distributor of 'Youth's Endearing Charm' is Mutual Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9815934300422668,
            "question": "Is 'Youth's Endearing Charm' a product of Mutual Film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9593427181243896,
            "question": "Besides 'Youth's Endearing Charm', what other films might Mutual Film have distributed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9560051560401917,
            "question": "Who distributed the movie 'Youth's Endearing Charm'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9211422204971313,
            "question": "What is the name of the film distribution company that released 'Youth's Endearing Charm'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9175249934196472,
            "question": "What role does Mutual Film play in the release of a film like 'Youth's Endearing Charm'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9093510508537292,
            "question": "Who might be the contact person at Mutual Film for information about 'Youth's Endearing Charm'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8792102932929993,
            "question": "Which company was responsible for distributing 'Youth's Endearing Charm'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7501551508903503,
            "question": "What company would have been involved in getting 'Youth's Endearing Charm' to theaters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6907709836959839,
            "question": "Can you name a film distributed by Mutual Film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6757208704948425,
            "question": "Mutual Film is known for distributing what kind of media?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The distributor of 'Youth's Endearing Charm' is Mutual Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6455_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a film distributed by Mutual Film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6455_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What company would have been involved in getting 'Youth's Endearing Charm' to theaters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6455_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which company was responsible for distributing 'Youth's Endearing Charm'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6455_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6455_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6455_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6455_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6455_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6455_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6455_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6455_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6455_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6455_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6455_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for your query:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. According to the document with file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6455/re-ranker-msmarco/18.txt, \"Youth's Endearing Charm\" is mentioned as one of Mary Miles Minter's motion pictures and a Mutual Star Production, along with Dulcie's Adventure, Faith, and A Dream or Two Ago. This suggests that Mutual Film was involved in the production and distribution of \"Youth's Endearing Charm\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n### Explanation:\nThe documents mention that \"Youth's Endearing Charm\" was a \"Mutual Star Production,\" which implies that Mutual Film Corp. distributed the film. Therefore, the statement that \"The distributor of 'Youth's Endearing Charm' is Mutual Film\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}